I've shown you how to create and I've
shown you how to retrieve. So we are now
on to update. How would I update
something in here? So let's go back to
our console. And if I want to access
local storage, then I'll say local
storage
dot set item. And if we access a key
that already exists, the thing that we
put in here will be um will overwrite
what was previously there. So if I say
take item hello and set it to new value
and I hit enter, if we come over here to
our application where it used to say
hello and then the value used to be
world, it is now a new value. Part of
the reason I chose to change that one is
because if we look in session storage,
session storage and local storage are
separate entities. So the hello key in
session storage is storing world. the
hello key in local storage is storing
new value. So I partially wanted to show
you um how to update a value but I also
wanted to show you this local storage
and session storage are two distinct
places to store information. And um if
we come over here if we want to change
session storage
um you do the same thing. You say set
item you look for an item that exists
and you set it to be something else. So
this will be my new value.
And if we hit enter now, if we come over
to our application um and we come into
session storage, you can see that hello
is now storing my new value instead of
storing the text world. And so that is
how you update values using local and
session